So now you've gathered the data to produce our second goal visualization,
现在 你已经收集了数据 可以完成第二个目标 可视化
the Roger Ebert Review Wordcloud.
Roger Ebert 影评的文字云
Next, we'd have to assess and clean the data.
接下来 我们得评估并清理数据
The second and third steps in the data wrangling process.
这是数据整理过程的第二步和第三步
This lesson is on gathering specifically though.
本节课讲述具体的收集方法
So we'll stay focused and leave assessing and cleaning to lessons three and four ahead.
所以 我们专注于此把数据评估和清理留在第三、四节课
I took care of both of these behind the scenes.
我会在备课时提前将这两项处理好
And the result of that is this master data frame here.
准备结果即为这里的主 DataFrame
Let's hop straight to the second final product here,
我们直接跳到第二个最终产物
the word clouds themselves.
即文字云
And here's a sample of them. On the right, E.T.
这里就是 word clouds 的示例
on the left, Inside Out.
右侧是 《ET 外星人》 左侧是 《头脑特工队》
E.T. was ranked 11th and Inside out was ranked 8th on that top 100 list.
在百佳电影排行榜中 《ET 外星人》 排在第 11 位 而 《头脑特工队》 排在第 8 位
I think this is so cool and I hope you do too.
我感觉这太酷了！希望你也感同身受
It's definitely a unique snapshot into the movie's plot and what
它是电影情节的一张快照
makes it great according to arguably the best film critic that ever lived.
据最佳影评人所说 海报是电影成功的一半
These movie posters pasted within the stencil
文字云模板中粘贴的这些电影海报
of this word cloud really do add some flash.
确实增光添彩
Let's check out a few more.
我们再多看几张
Here are some older classics.
此处是有些年代感的经典作品
On the left, Alfred Hitchcock's Rear Window, ranked 36.
左边是阿尔弗雷德·希区柯克的电影《后窗》 排在第 36 位
And on the right, Casablanca, ranked 16th.
右边《卡萨布兰卡》排在第 16 位
The colors here look so cool.
此处的色彩看上去很酷
I've never seen Rear Window but just from this word cloud and knowing
我从来没看过《后窗》但从文字云来看
Alfred Hitchcock is known for thriller or horror-type movies,
我们知道阿尔弗雷德·希区柯克因惊悚电影或恐怖类电影而出名
you can see danger and murder here.
你可以看到这部电影里充满危险和谋杀桥段
This word cloud has me itching to watch it.
文字云让我有一种迫不及待想要观看的感觉
Feel free to pause the video and take a look through these if you'd like.
如果感兴趣 暂停视频 快速浏览下
And here are two more.
还有两部电影
Wonder Woman and Star Wars: The Force Awakens.
《神奇女侠》和 《星球大战: 原力觉醒》
Wonder Woman ranked 46th and Star Wars ranked 62nd.
《神奇女侠》 排在第 46 位 星球大战排在第 62 位
And two more, Lala Land and Finding Nemo,
还有两部电影《爱乐之城》和《海底总动员》
ranked 86th and 73rd respectively.
分别排在第 86 位 和第 73 位
I can't get over the colors, they're just so pretty.
这色彩让我不能自拔太漂亮了
Data visualization can be informative,
数据可视化具有信息量大的特点
but it can also be art.
但也可以是一种艺术
So there are lots more of these word clouds.
还有很多文字云
So I'll put them all in a folder for you to download and check out if you're interested.
我将把它们放在一个文件夹中 以便你来下载 如果感兴趣可以去看看
These word clouds required gathering data from two different sources.
这些文字云需要从两个不同的来源收集数据
Downloading files from the internet, i.e.
从网上下载文件即 Roger Ebert 影评文本文件
the Roger Ebert review text files and accessing data from an API, i.e.
和从 API 访问得来的数据
the movie poster URLs.
电影海报 URL
And this data was in two formats,
和这个数据有两种格式
.txt and Json. Again, great work.
.txt 和 Json 还是得说 漂亮的作品